heroforge.com 2017-02-26

# None

Effective Date: This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated as of December 07, 2015.

This Privacy Policy describes:

  * how and why we collect certain information from you via the Website and the online services provided through the Website;
  * how we use and with whom we share such information;
  * how you can access and update such information; and
  * the choices you can make about how we collect, use and share your information

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by sending a notice to the email address that you have provided in connection with your Hero Forge account and/or by updating the Privacy Policy on our website and linking to it from our home page.

### Information We Collect

In order to purchase a Hero Forge miniature, you will need to create an account with our website. In order to register for a Hero Forge account and then make a purchase, you must provide the following personal information:

  * your name
  * your email address
  * a password that will be associated with your Hero Forge Accound
  * your mailing address
  * credit card and billing information which will be used to complete purchases from our website

Characters, figures, and prints created using our software is not considered personal or private information. We treat these designs and prints as public information which may be used or displayed publicly on our site, on other sites, in print, or in real life.

**Cookies:**   
We use cookies (or other similar technology), which are pieces of data on your computer tied to information about you which recognize you as a return user of the Website and help to provide a more personalized experience. Because we do not track personal information, we do not respond to do not track signals when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### How We Use and Share Your Personal Information

We may use the personal information we collect:

  * to register and service your Hero Forge account;
  * for our internal records, tracking and business purposes;
  * to fulfill your purchases of Hero Forge offerings;
  * in order to contact you about your order or account, or to respond to your requests for customer support;
  * to provide you with information regarding changes to the Hero Forge website; and
  * to inform you of any product or promotional offers we may have.

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * to third-party companies to perform services on our behalf, including marketing assistance, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and data analysis. We require all such third-party service providers to not use your personal information for any purpose other than to provide services to us.
  * to comply with any applicable, law, regulation, legal process or government request, to enforce our rights or to protect the safety and security of our website and users.
  * In the event Hero Forge undergoes a business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer your personal information to the successor organization in such transaction.

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. It utilizes the cookie and usage data of visitors to this website to track and examine the use of this URL and to prepare reports on the activities and performance of this URL and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Read Google's privacy policy for more information.   
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google, use cookies or other identifiers to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### How to Access and Update Your Personal Information

If you have created a Hero Forge account, you may review and make changes to certain of your personal information by logging into your Hero Forge account and updating your account profile. 

### Children Under 13

This Website is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from such children. Children under the age of 13 should not use our Website or our online services at any time. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will use reasonable efforts to erase such information from our records.
